Visual AIDS Institutional Records
Visual AIDS Archive
Visual AIDS Institutional Records
1988-2024
Visual AIDS Archive
10 Linear Feet
Biographical / Historical
Founded in 1988, Visual AIDS is the only contemporary arts organization fully committed to raising AIDS awareness and creating dialogue around HIV issues today, by producing and presenting visual art projects, exhibitions, public forums, and publications—while assisting artists living with HIV/AIDS. We are committed to preserving and honoring the work of artists with HIV/AIDS and the artistic contributions of the AIDS movement.
Scope and Contents
The Institutional Records collection consists of materials relating to the organizational history of Visual AIDS. The collection consists of papers, photographs, 35mm slides, exhibition materials, publications, promotional materials, periodicals, correspondence, buttons, collectible cards, condoms, press clippings, printed artworks, broadsides, postcards, and ephemera.
Arrangement
Materials in this collection are arranged by subject. Within subject, the folders are arranged chronologically by year and then alphabetically.
Related Materials
A collection of 53.75 linear feet of Visual AIDS institutional records were donated to NYU Fales Library and Special Collections in late June 2017. The finding aid for that collection can be found here: https://findingaids.library.nyu.edu/fales/mss_503/
- Administrative Files
  Biographical / Historical
  The Administrative Files series contains materials pertaining to the general operation and history of Visual AIDS outside of the specific categories represented by other series. This includes materials associated with organizational history, planning and development, general information sheets and promotional materials, and press about Visual AIDS as a whole.
  Scope and Contents
  These materials include papers, press clippings, correspondence, exhibition materials, promotional materials, buttons, ephemera, personnel files, and photographs. These materials are dated 1989-2012.
  - General Info Sheets, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Press Kits, 1989-2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Hate Mail, 1989-2017 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Patrick O'Connell Materials, 1994-2021 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Press Clippings, 1995-2018 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Materials, 1998-2019 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Visual AIDS Material in Exhibitions and Collections, 2004-2022 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Letterhead, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Organizational Planning Materials, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Early History (Compiled 2010) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Logo Redesign Materials, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Website Development Materials, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Projects
  - Archive Project
    In 1994, the artist Frank Moore and arts writer David Hirsh formed the Archive Project to protect the legacies of artists who were being lost to the AIDS crisis. Moore and Hirsh were joined by Roberto Juarez, Sur Rodney (Sur), Eric Rhein, Geoff Hendricks, Ken Chu, and David Cabrera in this endeavor, and the group soon merged with Visual AIDS. Artists were solicited to join the archive through flyers, posters, and personal outreach. Volunteer photographers would visit artists in their homes or studios to document and catalog their artwork, providing the artist with a copy of the slides and depositing a copy into the archive. Artists (and the friends and families of deceased artists) also contributed press clippings, resumes, exhibition cards and other biographical materials to their artist files. The collection that has developed out of this ongoing endeavor is now known as the Visual AIDS Artist Files collection.
    The Artist Registry is an online repository containing artwork by over 970 HIV+ artists. Created in November 2012 with digitized slides from the Visual AIDS Artist Files, the Registry is continuously growing, allowing anyone who self-identifies as an artist living with HIV to create a profile.
    Materials pertaining to the history and development of both the Archive Project and the Artist Registry are included in this sub-series.
    Materials pertaining to the Archive Project contain correspondence, promotional materials, exhibition materials, press clippings, photographs, development materials, periodicals, and papers. These materials are dated 1989-2005.
    - Press Clippings, 1989-1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Promotional Materials and Exhibition Announcements, 1989-1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Library Collection Development and Donation Solicitations, 1989-2007 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Planning Materials and Meeting Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Zine Materials, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Estate Project for Artists with AIDS, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Outreach and Promotional Materials, 1996-2013 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Art+ Newsletters, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Introductory Letters and Forms, 2000-2005 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Volunteer Photographer Materials, 2000-2005 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Web Gallery Materials, 2000-2010 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Artist Member Lists, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Artist Registry Development Materials, 2011-2012 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Artist Registry Agreement Development, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Artist Registry and Archive Statistics, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Research on HIV+ Artists, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Broadsides and Print Projects
    Since 1992, Visual AIDS has commissioned artists to create print projects that utilize artistic strategies to share information about the HIV and AIDS crisis. First conceived as a part of Day Without Art, the first Visual AIDS broadsides were intentionally easy to photocopy and distributed without copyright to encourage organizations to reproduce and disseminate them. In the decades since, the form of these print projects has expanded to include stickers, buttons, and larger newsprint broadsides.
    Materials pertaining to Visual AIDS Broadsides and Print Projects include copies of broadsides, production materials, correspondence, stickers, buttons, condoms, playing cards, collectible items, and promotional materials. These materials are dated 1992-2022.
    The materials in this sub-series are primarily arranged by artist or creator name.
    - Branch, Bradford, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Kruger, Barbara, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Ligon, Glenn, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Visual AIDS Artist Caucus, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Broadside Originals, 1992-1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Giorno, John, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Kellard, Adrian, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Melaney, Adamo Yuri, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Cullum, William, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Juarez, Roberto, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Taylor, Steed, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Parker, Mike, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Berg, Copy, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - "Spend Wisely. Fight AIDS.", 1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Weiss, Harvey, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - De Hoyos, Joe, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Farber, Neil, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Grant, Deborah, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Jackson, Derek, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Johanson, Chris, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Moyer, Carrie, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Carman, Curtis, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Lotuffo, Maria G., 2006 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Takahashi, Ginger Brooks, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Blake, Nayland, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Hanson, Erik, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Laurita, Lou, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Lemoins, Nancer, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Production and Outreach Materials, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Chaich, John, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Huh, Kate, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Lyons, Noah, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Mitchell, Michael, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Powhida, William, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Production and Outreach Materials, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Broadside Exhibition Announcements, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Production and Outreach Materials, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Reynolds, Hunter, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Wu, Ingrid Tsang, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Art Action AIDS E-Cards, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Print+ Projects Materials, 2012-2016 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Print+ Projects Promotional Cards, 2014-2019 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - "What is Undetectable?" Balloons, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Kelley, Shan Buttons, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - HIV Criminalization Broadside, 2018 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - fierce pussy Broadside, 2021 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Lemoins, Nancer Stickers, 2022 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Play Smart
      From 2010 to 2019, Visual AIDS produced Play Smart safer sex kits containing artist-created trading cards, condoms, and lube. The trading cards included straightforward information about HIV testing, pre and post exposure prophylaxis, and other harm reduction strategies. Play Smart kits were distributed freely in bars, queer spaces, and art institutions. The project was developed in conversation with Dr. Demetre Daskalakis at The Men's Sexual Health Project (M*SHP). Organizations like Streetwise & Safe, Sero Project, GMHC, SRLP, and Callen-Lorde collaborated in developing and distributing Play Smart nationally.
      Materials pertaining to Play Smart campaigns include correspondence, press clippings, promotional materials, event programs, and press clippings. These materials are dated 2005-2019.
      - Condom Ordering Materials, 2005-2007 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Participant Materials, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Press Clippings, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - Production Materials and Correspondence, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 50)
      - Promotional Materials, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Production Materials, 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Distribution Materials, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Press Clippings, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Production Materials and Correspondence, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Production Materials and Correspondence, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Launch Event Programs, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Event Programs, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Launch Event Programs, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Press Clippings, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - "I Serve Art" Exhibition Materials, 2015 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - 2011 Play Smart Cards (Card Box 1)
      - 2012 Play Smart Cards (Card Box 1)
      - 2013 Play Smart Cards (Card Box 1)
      - 2014 Play Smart Cards (Card Box 1)
      - 2015 Play Smart Cards (Card Box 2)
      - 2019 Play Smart Cards (Card Box 2)
  - Day Without Art
    In 1989, in response to the worsening AIDS crisis and coinciding with the World Health Organization's second annual World AIDS Day on December 1, Visual AIDS organized the first Day Without Art. A committee of art workers (curators, writers, and art professionals) sent out a call for "mourning and action in response to the AIDS crisis" that would celebrate the lives and achievements of lost colleagues and friends; encourage caring for all people with AIDS; educate diverse publics about HIV; and call for a cure. More than 800 arts organizations, museums and galleries throughout the U.S. participated by shrouding artworks and replacing them with information about HIV and safer sex, locking their doors or dimming their lights, and producing exhibitions, programs, readings, memorials, rituals, and performances. Visual AIDS coordinated this network mega-event by producing a poster and handling promotion and press relations.
    During the early nineties, as artists became more intimately involved with the group, Visual AIDS initiated numerous projects that included: A Night Without Light (the dimming of the New York skylight); Electric Blanket (a nationwide outdoor slide projection with text and images); Positive Actions (an exhibition-competition for a television PSA held simultaneously in three NYC venues); the Broadside Project (distribution of copyright-free text and images by well-known artists targeted to specific audiences); and ambitious media collaborations, including AIDS Timeline by Group Material and national televised events. Artists created many of the most moving actions, including Robert Farber's audio work "Every Ten Minutes". By the mid-90's, Day Without Art attracted more than 8000 participants throughout the world.
    Since 2010, Visual AIDS has worked with artists and filmmakers to internationally distribute videos to museums, art institutions, schools and AIDS organizations for Day Without Art. Since 2014, Visual AIDS has commissioned and distributed a video program for Day With(out) Art, coordinating screenings at over 100 venues around the world.
    Materials pertaining to Day Without Art contain exhibition announcements, photographs, 35mm slides, correspondence, promotional materials, exhibition planning materials, press clippings, periodicals, exhibition programs, and publications. These materials are dated 1989-2022.
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Louise Lawler Helms Amendment Exhibition Materials, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Participant List, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Participant Press Releases and Promotional Materials, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Photographs, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Planning Materials, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Political Action, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Press Releases and Promotional Materials, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Press Clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - World AIDS Day Newsletters, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Stationery and Logos, 1989-1994 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Group Materials AIDS Timeline Exhibition Materials, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Group Material AIDS Timeline Magazine Project Clippings, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Group Materials AIDS Timeline Magazine Project Planning Materials, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Homeless Women and AIDS, Hope Sandrow Materials, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Logo Materials, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Promotional Materials, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Visual AIDS Artist Caucus, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Exhibition Slides, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - "Electric Blanket" (1 of 2), 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - "Electric Blanket" (2 of 2), 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - "Electric Blanket" Photographs, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - "Night Without Light", 1990-1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Photographs, 1990-1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Poster and Broadside 35mm Slides, 1990-1998 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - City of New York Proclamations, 1990-2002 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings, 1990-2011 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - "Connecting Lives" Exhibition at PS 122, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Bravo "Unfinished Stories" Materials, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Participant Press Releases, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Press Kits, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Project Replication Outline, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Promotional Materials, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Robert Farber "Every Ten Minutes", 1991 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - The Witness Project, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Women's Action Materials, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Names Quilt Education Gallery Slides, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Promotional Materials, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - REPOHistory Photographs, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Press Releases and Participant Materials, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Exhibition Announcements, 1993-2014 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Promotional Materials and Correspondence, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Surveys, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Contact Lists, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Political Correspondence, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Princeton University, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Promotional Materials, 1995-1998 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Call for Proposals, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Periodicals, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Programs and Press, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Speakers Bureau Materials, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - "Reflections on Day Without Art", 2000-2006 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Participant Forms, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - "Video Positive" Bronx Museum of Art, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - "The Big Nothing" ICA Philadelphia, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Press Clippings, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Press Clippings, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Press Clippings, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Press Clippings, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Ira Sachs "Last Address", 2010 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Press Clippings, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Jim Hodges "Untitled", 2010-2011 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - "Not Over - Red Ribbon Project" Materials, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Participant Materials and Correspondence (1 of 2), 2011 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Participant Materials and Correspondence (2 of 2), 2011 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Jim Hubbard "United in Anger", 2012 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Participant Forms, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - fierce pussy "For the Record", 2013 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - "Alternate Endings" Materials, 2014-2015 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - "Radiant Presence" Materials, 2015 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - "Compulsive Practice" Materials, 2016 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - "Alternate Endings, Radical Beginnings" Materials, 2016 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Press Clippings, 2017 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Japanese Translation of Materials, 2017-2019 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - "Alternate Endings, Activist Risings" Materials, 2018 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - "Still Beginning", 2019 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - "Transmissions", 2020 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - "Enduring Care" Materials, 2021 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - "Being and Belonging" Programs, 2022 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Exhibitions
    After the founding of the Archive Project in 1994, Visual AIDS began to organize exhibitions to present work by artists living with HIV. The organization's first exhibitions focused solely on artists represented in its archive. In the late 1990s, Visual AIDS exhibition program shifted towards curated group exhibitions that examine the deep cultural history of the AIDS crisis and contemporary issues around HIV/AIDS. These exhibitions have included both HIV positive and HIV negative artists. Guest curators have included Julia Bryan-Wilson, Dean Daderko, Sur Rodney (Sur), Jean Carlomusto, Alexandra Juhasz, Hugh Ryan, Josh Lubin Levy & Ricardo Montez. Visual AIDS has never operated its own exhibition space, instead partnering with galleries, non-profits, and community spaces to mount exhibitions. Exhibition partners have included La MaMa Galleria, The 8th Floor, Printed Matter, Artists Space, The Painting Center, Real Art Ways, Boston Center for the Arts, Fales Library and Special Collections, Aljira, P.S. 122, Transformer Gallery, Elizabeth Foundation for the Arts, and MoCADA, among others.
    Materials pertaining to Visual AIDS exhibitions contain exhibition announcements, exhibition planning materials, promotional materials, correspondence, photographs, and press clippings. These materials are dated 1989-2021.
    - "The First 10" at PS 122 Gallery, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - "Works from the Archive Project" at God's Love We Deliver, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - "Arts' Communities/AIDS Communities" at BCA Cyclorama, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - "A Living Testament of the Blood Fairies" at Artists Space, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - "not sacred" at The Nathan Cummings Foundation, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - "The Cocktail" at Flamingo East, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - "Mapping No Boundaries: Art. AIDS. Action." Materials, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - "Salon" at the National Arts Club, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - "Desire" at Syracuse University, Robert B Menschel Photography Gallery, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - "Bodies of Resistance" at Real Art Ways, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - "Lightbox" Materials, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - "20 Years - It's Closer Than You Think" at GMHC Gallery, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - "Pull Up a Chair" at GMHC Gallery, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - "Sight of Construction" at The LGBT Center, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - "Go Figure" at The LGBT Center, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - "Share Your Vision" at Artists Space, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Promotional and Press Materials (Various Exhibitions), 2003 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - "Release" and "Release II" at MoCADA, 2003-2005 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - "Between Ten" at SPIN Gallery, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - "Side x Side" at La MaMa Galleria, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - "Side x Side" Press Clippings, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - "Tainted Love" at La MaMa Galleria, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - "Tainted Love" Press Clippings, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - "You Make Me Feel (Mighty Real)" at NYU Fales Library, 2009-2010 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - "To Believe" at La MaMa Galleria, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - NADA Materials, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - "Mixed Messages" at La MaMa Galleria (1 of 2), 2011 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - "Mixed Messages" at La MaMa Galleria (2 of 2), 2011 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - "Mixed Messages" Press Clippings, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - "Mixed Messages" Sign In Sheet, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - "The Sword of Damocles" at The Painting Center, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - "ReMixed Messages" at Fathom Gallery, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - "Undetectable" at La MaMa Galleria, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Arch Connelly at La MaMa Galleria Loan Agreements, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - "Not Over" at La MaMa Galleria (1 of 2), 2013 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Not Over" at La MaMa Galleria (2 of 2), 2013 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Not Over" Press Clippings, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Ephemera as Evidence" at La MaMa Galleria, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Party Out of Bounds" at La MaMa Galleria, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Pulse Miami Materials, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Everyday" at La MaMa Galleria, 2016 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - "Persons of Interest" at Bureau of General Services – Queer Division, 2016 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - "Pulse New York" Materials, 2016 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Exhibition Proposals, 2016 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - "Voice = Survival" at The 8th Floor, 2017 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - "Cell Count" at La MaMa Galleria, 2018 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - "Altered After" at Participant, Inc, 2019 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - "Comic Velocity" at PS 122 Gallery, 2021 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - "Comic Velocity" Materials - "Just a Pill?", 2021 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - "Comic Velocity" Materials - "Legalize Positivity", 2021 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - "Comic Velocity" Materials - "Paco", 2021 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - "Comic Velocity" Materials - "Strutting to Stop Stigma", 2021 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Public Programs
    Visual AIDS produces numerous public events and programs, often partnering with other organizations and museums. The Public Programs series contains announcements, handouts, and internal documents related to panels, book fairs, and other public events that Visual AIDS organized or participated in.
    Materials pertaining to Visual AIDS Public Programs include exhibition and program announcements, promotional materials, planning materials, ephemera, and event programs. These materials are dated 2008-2022.
    - "Graphic Alert" Materials, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - 2004 Public Programs (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - "AIDS/Art/Work" Materials, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - 2005 Public Programs (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 2007 Public Programs (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - "Art, AIDS, America" Colloquium, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - "Festival for Ideas for the New City" Materials, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - 2011 Public Programs (Box 8, Folder 5)